# DAVID PLEITEZ

David.pleitez1012@icloud.com | 702-927-5148 | Las Vegas, NV 89103

St	ımma	arv
----	------	-----

Customer-focused Associate with solid understanding of sales dynamics, marketing and customer service. Offering 1-2 years of experience providing quality product recommendations and solutions to meet customer needs and exceed expectations. Organized and motivated employee eager to apply time management and organizational skills in various environments. Seeking entry-level opportunities to expand skills while facilitating company growth.

#### Skills

- Brand awareness
- Communication skills
- Relationship management
- Revenue generation
- Team building
- Active listening
- Computer skills
- Work ethic

- Flexible
- Time management
- Customer Support
- Customer Service
- Problem Resolution
- Bilingual Spanish and English
- Verbal Communication
- Adaptive team player

### Experience

#### Learning Ambassador | Amazon - Las Vegas, NV | 01/2021 - Current

- Delivered feedback using positive reinforcement techniques to encourage, motivate and build confidence in associates.
- Completed in-depth research for numerous technical issues and helped establish procedures to prevent repetitive problems.
- Instructed associates on proper utilization of computers and class-related technology.

Inbound Stower | Amazon - Las Vegas, NV | 05/2020 - 01/2021

- Used handheld scanner to sort products onto appropriate shelves daily.
- Inspected incoming material before scanning it and separated defective items with 100% accuracy.
- Continuously pulled items weighing up to 50 pounds off carts and placed on correct shelves.

Sales Associate | Forever 21 - Las Vegas, NV | 10/2019 - 05/2020

- Helped average of 100 customers per day by responding to inquiries and locating products.
- Arranged new merchandise with signage and appealing displays to encourage customer sales and move overstock items.
- Facilitated positive guest experiences by promptly locating desired items for customers.

## Education and Training

Durango High School | Las Vegas, NV | 05/2018

High School Diploma

Languages
-----------

Spanish:	English:			
Native/ Bilingual	Native/ Bilingual			
Activities and Honors				

Top five in stowing & in UPH (units per hour) Hobbies include sports, music, reading, movies, & collecting vinyl.